Robert S. McNamara Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Classified, 1962-2002 (Box II:CL 1)
  - Speeches and Writings
    - Documentary films
      - The Fog of War
        - Background and research material
          - Secretary of defense
            - Notes and miscellaneous documents, 1968 (Container II:114)
    - Writings by others
      - Articles and miscellaneous writings
        - Brown, Christopher
          - Correspondence, 1963-1967, 2000 (Container II:125) See also Top Secret
- Part II: Top Secret, 1963-1967, 2000 (Box II:TS 1)
  Correspondence, background and research material, and related items.
  - Speeches and Writings (Box II: TS 1)
    - Books
      - In Retrospect
        - Background and research material
          - Chapter 8, “The Christmas Bombing Pause,” 1966
    - Writings by others
      - Articles and miscellaneous writings
        - Brown, Christopher
          - Correspondence, 1963-1967, 2000
- Part II: Formerly Restricted Data, 2002 (Box II:FRD 1)
  Review.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the item was removed.
  - Subject File
    - Defense department
      - Nuclear Posture Review, 2002
- Part II: Sensitive Compartmented Information, 1962 (Box II:SCI 1)
  Report.
  - Subject File (Box II:SCI 1)
    - Cuban Missile Crisis
      - Originals and copies of primary documents
        - Miscellany, 1962
- Part II: Oversize, 1994 (Box II:OV 1)
  Genealogical blueprints of the Strange family of Virginia.
  - Speeches and Writings (Box II:OV 1)
    - Books
      - In Retrospect
        - Background and research material
          - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Container II:95)